{
  "Presentacion":
  {
    "Titulo":"Drag and Drop",
    "Descripcion":"Definitely, the best option for the job is John Brown, but he will have to adapt to the schedules at the office. Help me organize his routine activities in a logical order. Drag the activities to the blank spaces."
  },
  "Actividad":
  [
    {
      "Pregunta":"I wake up",
      "Respuesta":"1"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I take a shower",
      "Respuesta":"2"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I get dressed",
      "Respuesta":"3"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I have breakfast",
      "Respuesta":"4"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I get to work",
      "Respuesta":"5"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I have lunch",
      "Respuesta":"6"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I finish work",
      "Respuesta":"7"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I go back home",
      "Respuesta":"8"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I have dinner",
      "Respuesta":"9"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"I go to bed",
      "Respuesta":"10"
    }
  ],
  "Enunciado" :[
    {
      "Item":"6:30 am"
    },
    {
      "Item":"6:45 am"
    },
    {
      "Item":"7:00 am"
    },
    {
      "Item":"7:15 am"
    },
    {
      "Item":"8:00 am"
    },
    {
      "Item":"1:00 pm"
    },
    {
      "Item":"5:00 pm"
    },
    {
      "Item":"5:30 pm"
    },
    {
      "Item":"9:00 pm"
    },
    {
      "Item":"10:30 pm"
    }
  ],    
  "Retroalimentacion":
  {
    "Bien":"Excellent! You can now identify the main actions of Johnâ€™s routine. Is yours similar?",
    "Mal":"Try again! Think about your own routine. It must not be too different from yours."
  },
 "Botones":
 {
    "limpiar":"Clear",
    "enviar":"Send",
    "siguiente":"Next",
    "repetir":"Re"
 }
}